{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:P..P.all.10.rand.say.54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299254275","data":{"timestamp":" 947299254275"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054014"," gameId":" 77793334-2c2d-45fa-b169-822d4cea1f6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_P..P.all.10.rand.say.54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_t_i_p"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:P..P.all.10.rand.say.54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299260919","data":{"timestamp":" 947299260919"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054014"," gameId":" 77793334-2c2d-45fa-b169-822d4cea1f6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_P..P.all.10.rand.say.54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ch_p_g"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:P..P.all.10.rand.say.54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299268456","data":{"timestamp":" 947299268455"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054014"," gameId":" 77793334-2c2d-45fa-b169-822d4cea1f6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_P..P.all.10.rand.say.54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ch_p_g"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:P..P.all.10.rand.say.54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299278903","data":{"timestamp":" 947299278903"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054014"," gameId":" 77793334-2c2d-45fa-b169-822d4cea1f6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_P..P.all.10.rand.say.54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ch_p_g"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:P..P.all.10.rand.say.54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299285515","data":{"timestamp":" 947299285515"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054014"," gameId":" 77793334-2c2d-45fa-b169-822d4cea1f6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_P..P.all.10.rand.say.54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_h_ch_p"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:P..P.all.10.rand.say.54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299292164","data":{"timestamp":" 947299292164"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054014"," gameId":" 77793334-2c2d-45fa-b169-822d4cea1f6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_P..P.all.10.rand.say.54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_h_p_ch"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:P..P.all.10.rand.say.54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299299645","data":{"timestamp":" 947299299645"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054014"," gameId":" 77793334-2c2d-45fa-b169-822d4cea1f6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_P..P.all.10.rand.say.54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_h_p_ch"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:P..P.all.10.rand.say.54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299310091","data":{"timestamp":" 947299310091"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054014"," gameId":" 77793334-2c2d-45fa-b169-822d4cea1f6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_P..P.all.10.rand.say.54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_h_p_ch"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:P..P.all.10.rand.say.54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299316287","data":{"timestamp":" 947299316287"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054014"," gameId":" 77793334-2c2d-45fa-b169-822d4cea1f6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_P..P.all.10.rand.say.54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_d_o_p"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:P..P.all.10.rand.say.54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299322872","data":{"timestamp":" 947299322872"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054014"," gameId":" 77793334-2c2d-45fa-b169-822d4cea1f6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_P..P.all.10.rand.say.54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_p_y_e"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:P..P.all.10.rand.say.54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299324348","data":{"timestamp":" 947299324348"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054014"," gameId":" 77793334-2c2d-45fa-b169-822d4cea1f6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_P..P.all.10.rand.say.54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_p_y_e"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947299407423","data":{"timestamp":" 947299407422"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_054014"," gameId":" 77793334-2c2d-45fa-b169-822d4cea1f6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_P..P.all.10.rand.say.54"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_p_y_e"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}